有一个全新的头目登场 她的名字叫莉莉丝
Here is a big new comer.Her name is Lilith.
我想我不会在喜欢你了
I don't think I like you any more.
我身体里流淌着恶魔之血 迪恩
I have got demon blood in me, dean.
我是一个全新级别的怪物
I am whole new level of freak.
等等 她不是露比 是莉莉丝
Wait! It's not Ruby, its Lilith.
小可爱们 上吧
Sic him, boys.
你应该给我放尊重点
You should show me some respect.
我能带你出来
I dragged you out of hell.
也能再把你扔回去
I can throw you back in.
快跑
Run!
它会杀了你
It'll kill you!
[邪恶力量 第4季第6集]
（43小时之前）
泰勒探员 佩里探员 认识下弗兰克·奥布赖恩
Agent tyler, agent perry, meet frank o'brien.
他是因突发心脏病而死的 是吗
He died of a heart attack, right?
三天前的事了
Three days ago.
但是奥布赖恩才44岁 而且据资料上显示
But o'brien was 44 years old and, according to this.
他还是一名马拉松选手
a marathon runner.
人迟早都会死的
Everybody drops dead sooner or later.
这也是我为什么要找有安全感的工作
It's why I got job security.
是吗 如果弗兰克因心脏猝死是意外
Yeah, but frank kicked it here.
那眼下 就在昨天 莫米饭店也有两个完全健康的人猝死于此
Now, just yesterday, two perfectly healthy men bit it in maumee.
全都是突发性心脏病 你不觉得奇怪吗
All heart attacks. you don't think that's strange?
就我看来这是莫米饭店的问题
Sounds like maumee's problem to me.
为什么FBI总是要找个垫背的
Why's the FBI give a damn, anyway?
我们只想看看弗兰克的尸检报告
We just want to see the results of frank's autopsy.
哪儿来的尸检报告
What autopsy?
你马上会做的那份
The one you're gonna do.
第一次现场尸检
First dead body?
我可不想靠近它
Far from it.
噢 好了
Oh, good.
这些肌肉都已经僵硬了
Because these suckers can get pretty ripe.
嘿 麻烦你把肋骨钳递给我 行吗
Hey, hand me those rib cutters, would you?
这些是婚戒造成的
Is that from a wedding ring?
- 我可不认为弗兰克是已婚人士 - 这我就管不了了
- I didn't think frank was married. - Ain't my department.
那你觉得这些是怎么造成的
Any idea how he got these?
你要知道
You know what?
你越是垂死挣扎 事实上你死得越快
When you drop dead, you actually tend to drop.
可能是挣扎时身体接触地面产生的擦痕
Body probably got scraped up when it hit the ground.
怎么了
What?
我 我没发现任何主动脉阻塞的现象
I-i can't find any blockages in any of the major arteries.
这心脏看起来根本就没有任何问题
Heart looks pretty damn healthy.
你能暂时帮忙拿一下吗 劳驾
Hold that a second, would you?
噢 抱歉 那是脾脏液
Oh, sorry. spleen juice.
该死的警钟 莱纳斯 你看到我的 他们是谁
Hell's bells, linus, have you seen my… Who are they?
- 联邦调查局的探员 我 - 你居然让他们这么等着
- Federal agents. I, uh - And you kept them waiting?
是你 是你说的别打扰你嘛
You… you said not to disturb.
快进来 小伙子们
Come on back, fellas.
脱鞋先
Shoes off.
艾尔·布莱敦
Al britton.
- 很高兴见到你们 - 我们也是
- Good to meet you. - You too.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了
Okay.
那么
So…
那我能为萨姆大叔（美国绰号）做些啥
What can I do for uncle Sam?
嗯 我们正在调查弗兰克·奥布赖恩一死之事
Well, we're looking into the death of frank o'brien.
我们知道是你的人发现了他的尸体
We understand some of your men found his body.
是的
They did.
我跟弗兰克 是挚友
Me and frank, we were friends.
该死的 我们俩都是斗鸡队的（迪恩误会成召妓了）
Hell, we were gamecocks.
那是我们垒球队的名字
That's our softball team's name.
他们都强壮的物种
They're majestic animals.
我和弗兰克在高中时就认识了
I knew frank since high school.
老实说 我都是到了今天早上才有勇气去看他
To be honest, I just this morning got up the strength to go see him.
弗兰克是
Frank was…
他是一个好人
He was a good man.
是的
Yeah.
诚心的
Big heart.
在他死前 你有没注意到弗兰克有什么奇怪的地方
Before he died, did you notice frank acting strange?
比如害怕什么
Maybe scared of something?
噢 该死的 是的
Oh, hell, yeah.
非常的神经质
Real jumpy.
那你知道他究竟害怕什么吗
You know what scared him?
不知道
No.
也不接电话
Wouldn't answer his phone.
最后 我派了我手下去看看他 结果
Finally, i sent some of my boys over to check on him, and, well,
剩下的你们也都知道
You know the rest.
对了 联邦调查据干嘛管这些个小事
So, why the feds give a crap?
你们不会真的认为这里会发生什么大案吧
You don't really think there's a case here?
不 不是
- No, - no.
那没什么特别
It's probably nothing.
只是突发性心脏病罢了
Just a heart attack.
那不可能是什么突发性心脏病
No way that was a heart attack.
当然不是
Definitely no way.
三名受害者都有相同的红色抓痕
Three victims, all with those same red scratches,
都在48小时之内由紧张到惊恐至死
All went from jittery to terrified to dead within 48 hours.
一定有什么吓死了他们
Something scared them to death?
好吧 那么 什么东西可以做到这一点呢
All right, so, what can do that?
什么东西不能呢
What can't?
鬼魂 吸血鬼 卓柏卡布拉
Ghosts, vampires, chupacabra?
- 这样的东西多着呢 - 对
- It could be a hundred things. - Yeah.
那么我们就得理个清单出来一样一样排除
So we make a list and start crossing things off.
好的 最后见到弗兰克·奥布赖恩的人是谁来着
All right, who's the last person to see frank o'brien alive?
嗯 他的邻居 马克·哈金森
Uh, his neighbor, mark hutchins.
- 停下 嘿 - 咋啦
- Hang on, hey. - What?
我不喜欢看到那些年轻小子聚在那儿
I don't like the looks of those teenagers down there.
我们走这边
Let's walk this way.
泰勒和佩里
Tyler and perry.
跟阿罗史密斯（硬摇滚乐队）一样
Just like aerosmith.
是的 世界果真很小
Yeah, small world.
那么 你醉后见到弗兰克·奥布赖恩的时间是
So, the last time you saw frank o'brien?
星期一 他正从他家窗户那边望着我
Monday. he was watching me from his window.
我想他挥挥手 但他马上就把窗帘拉上了
I waved at him, but he just closed the curtains.
嗯哼 那你最近有和他交谈过吗
Hmm. did you speak to him recently?
或是他看起来有什么不一样吗
Did he seem different?
嗯 像是很惊恐啊
Uh, scared?
噢 完全正确 他很害怕出门
Oh, totally. he was freaking out.
那你知道 嗯 你知道他害怕什么吗
Do you know, uh, do you know what scared him?
嗯 当然 女巫啊
Well, yeah, witches.
女巫
Witches?
就像是
Like…?
嗯 前些晚上电视里上演了绿野仙踪 不是吗
Well, "wizard of oz" was on tv the other night, right?
之后他就说那个绿衣小贱人想要抓他
And he said that green bitch was totally out to get him.
还有其他让他害怕的吗
Anything else scare him?
所有的一切都让他害怕 象基地组织 侦探 人造糖
Everything else scared him, al-qaeda, ferrets, artificial sweetener,
甚至于那些睁着小眼睛死鱼 反正就是所有的一切
Those pez dispensers with their dead little eyes, lots of stuff.
告诉我 弗兰克长什么样
So, tell me, what was frank like?
我是说 他死了 你知道吧
I mean, he's dead, you know?
我不想打击他 但他好多了
I-i don't want to hammer him, but he got better.
他好多了
He got better?
他在高中时 他算个鸟
Well, in high school he was… he was a dick.
算个鸟
A dick?
像个傻逼一样
Like a bully.
我是说 他可能被镇上一般的人取笑过
I mean, he probably taped half the town's butt cheeks together,
也包括我在内
Mine included.
所以他看别人也不爽
So he pissed a lot of people off.
你是说可能有人要报复
You think anyone would have wanted to get revenge?
我不确定
Well, i don't…
弗兰克有心脏病是吧
Frank had a heart attack, right?
回答问题 先生
Just answer the question, sir.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
我说了 他媳妇出事以后他就好多了
Like I said, he got better after what happened to his wife.
他媳妇
His wife?
他结婚了那么
So he was married.
她20年前就去世了
She died about 20 years ago.
弗兰克很受打击
Frank was really broken up about it.
不要怕多尼
Don't be scared of donny.
他只是小宝贝
He's a sweetheart.
这是你一定得看看的玛丽
It's marie you got to look out for.
她好像挺害怕
She smells fear.
郡秘书办公室有什么发现吗
Any luck at the county clerk's office?
我不确定是否称之为运气
I'm not sure I'd call it luck.
弗兰克的老婆 杰西 是个狂躁抑郁症病人
Frank's wife, jessie, was a manic-depressive.
她1988年离家出走就此渺无音讯
She went off her meds back in '88 and vanished.
他们两周后找到了她 在三个村外
They found her two weeks later, three towns over,
缩在旅馆里 自杀了
Strung up in her motel room, suicide.
弗兰克没有阻止她什么的
Any chance frank helped her along to the other side?
没 她走的时候弗兰克在值夜班
No, frank was working the swing shift when she disappeared.
真他妈是完美的不在场证明
Airtight alibi.
他的本子上有什么记载
How was frank's pad?
屁都没有
Clean.
从头到尾看看
Searched it top to bottom.
没有咒语 没有魔袋 没有白银
No emf, no hex bags, no silver.
所以可能没有鬼魂 没有巫婆 也没有恶魔
So probably no ghosts, no witches, no demons.
排除三个可能 还有97个
3 down and 97 to go. yeah.
哥们 你速度快低于20了
Dude, you're going 20.
所以
And?
这是速度下限
That's the speed limit.
啥 安全行车也犯法啊
What? safety's a crime now?
哥们 你要去哪啊 刚才过我们旅馆了
Dude, where are you going? that was our hotel.
萨姆 我不会在迎面的车流中左拐的
Sam, i'm not gonna make a left-hand turn into oncoming traffic.
我不会自杀的
I'm not suicidal.
我有这么话说吗
Did I just say that?
奇了怪了
That was kind of weird.
你听见什么了吗
Do you hear something?
我被附身了
Am I haunted?
我被附身了？
Am I haunted?!
好的 鲍比 继续观察
Ok bobby.keep looking.
哥们
Dude.
看这个
Look at this.
我刚和鲍比说过话 所以
I just talked to bobby. and?
你不会喜欢它的
Um, well, you're not gonna like it.
啥
What?
幽灵疾病
It's ghost sickness.
幽灵疾病 是啊
Ghost sickness? yeah.
神啊 别 是的
God, no. yeah.
我都不知道这是什么 好吧
I don't even know what that is. okay.
一些文明相信某些幽灵
Some cultures believe that certain spirits.
可以感染活着的生物
Can infect the living with a disease, which is.
这就是为什么他们停在在屋里展出尸体
Why they stopped displaying bodies in houses.
并把他们从殡仪馆搬出去
And started taking them off to funeral homes.
好吧 做点好事吧
Okay, get to the good stuff.
你开始有焦虑症状了
Symptoms are you get anxious…
是啊 害怕还有 真的害怕 然后你的心就不跳了
Yeah. …and scared, then really scared, then your heart gives out.
熟悉吧
Sound familiar?
是啊 但是 萨姆 我们几周都没看见一个鬼魂
Yeah, but, sam, we haven't seen a ghost in weeks.
我怀疑你被鬼魂感染了
Well, i doubt you caught it from a ghost.
瞧 一旦幽灵感染第一个人
Look, once a spirit infects that first person,
幽灵疾病可以通过任何像咳嗽握手之类的行为传播
Ghost sickness can spread like any sickness through a cough, a handshake,
管他呢
Whatever.
如同流感一样
It's like the flu.
现在 弗兰克 奥布莱恩是第一个死的
Now, frank o'brien was the first to die,
说明他也可能是第一个感染的
Which means he was probably the first infected.
没有一个病人
Patient zero.
我们自己找的麻烦
Our very own outbreak monkey.
好吧 你看 弗兰克在莫米酒吧度过周末的
Right. get this, frank was in maumee over the weekend.
垒球联赛
Softball tournament…
他在这里至少感染了两个人
Which is where he must have infected the other two victims.
他们是战鸡队吗
Were they gamecocks?
玉米垃圾队的
Cornjerkers.
所以鬼魂感染了弗兰克 他传给另外俩人
So, ghosts infected frank, he passed it on to the other guys,
我又被他尸体感染了 对
And I got it from his corpse? right.
现在距离我神经失常心跳停止就两天时间了
So now, what, i have 48 hours before I go insane and my heart stops?
可能就一天
More like 24.
- 真快 - 没错
- Super. - Yeah.
为什么是我 不是你
Well, why me? why not you?
我是说 你也接触尸液了
I mean, you got hit with the spleen juice.
你看 鲍比和我研究了一下
Yeah, um, you see, bobby and I have a theory about that, too.
原因就是一个病原体会毒害三个受害者 个人体质问题
Turns out all three victims shared a certain, uh, personality type.
弗兰克是第一个中着的
Frank was a bully.
另两个受害者 一个副校长
The other two victims, one was a vice principal,
另一个是保镖
The other was a bouncer.
好吧
Okay.
基本上 他们都是白痴
Basically, they were all dicks.
你是说我也是白痴对吧
So you're saying I'm a dick?
不是不是
No, no, no.
这个推理不成立
It's not just that.
所有的三个受害者都因为害怕
All three victims used fear as a weapon,
现在这种疾病开始回报了
And now this disease is just returning the favor.
我没有吓唬人
I don't scare people.
迪恩 我们做的都是在吓唬人
Dean, all we do is scare people.
好吧 所以你也是白痴
Okay, well, then, you're a dick, too.
很明显 不管怎样 我不是
Apparently, i'm not. whatever.
我们怎么阻止它
How do we stop it?
我们解决掉传染源的鬼魂
We gank the ghost that started all this.
这样 这种病就没了
We do that, the disease should clear up.
你是说弗兰克的老婆
You thinking frank's wife?
你知道她为什么自杀吗
Who knows why she killed herself, you know?
你等在这里干什么
What are you doing waiting out here, anyway?
我们房间在4楼
Our room's on the fourth floor.
很 很高
It's… it's high.
我去试试换底楼的房间
I'll see if I can move us down to the first.
好的
Thanks. sure.
没事吧
Everything all right?
没事
Oh, yeah.
有点擦伤
Just peachy.
- 有发现么 - 有
- Find anything? - Yeah.
杰西 奥布莱恩的遗体已经烧了
Jessie o'brien's body was cremated,
我非常确定她不是我们要找的
So I'm pretty sure she is not our ghost.
嘿
Hey.
别挠了
Quit picking at that.
- 觉得如何 - 感觉好极
- How you feeling? - Awesome.
再次做砧板上的鱼肉的感觉真好
It's nice to have my head on the chopping block again.
我都快忘了这种感觉
I almost forgot what that feels like. yeah.
真妈的爽
It's freaking delightful.
我们继续努力
We'll keep looking.
你没事吧
You okay?
迪恩
Dean.
我们忽略的最大的线索 你
We've been completely ignoring the biggest clue we have, you.
我不想当线索
I don't want to be a clue.
擦痕 这个瘟疫要告诉我们一些事情
The abrasions, this, the disease, it's trying to tell us something.
告诉我们什么 小木块
Tell us what, wood chips?
正确
Exactly.
我才不要进去
I'm not going in there.
我要增援 你是唯一在这里的
I need backup, and you're all I've got.
你必须进去
You're going in, dean.
走吧
Let's do this.
有点让人毛骨悚然吧
It is a little spooky, isn't it?
我才不拿枪
Oh, i'm not carrying that.
会走火
It could go off.
我拿手电筒
I'll man the flashlight.
随便你
You do that.
感应器不会和我在一起就有反映了吧
Emf's not gonna work with me around, is it?
别这么说
You don't say.
继续
Come on.
什么
What, shh.
给弗兰克 爱你的 杰西
"to frank. love, jessie."
弗兰克的戒指
Frank o'brien's ring.
弗兰克来这里干什么
What the hell was frank doing here?
不知道
No idea.
真吓人
That was scary!
等等
Wait.
卢瑟 加兰
Luther garland.
嘿 这是
Hey, this is, uh…
是弗兰克的老婆
…this is frank's wife.
那东西的一部分
Plot thickens.
对
Yeah…
怎么回事
But into what?
我们来对地方了
Guess we got the right place.
他喝醉了么
Is he…drunk?
没有
No.
副警官 根据这个
Deputy, according to this,
卢瑟 加兰死于精神病
Luther garland's cause of death was physical trauma.
什么意思
What does that mean?
一个死于20年前我还没出生的人
The guy died 20 years ago, before my time.
不好意思
Sorry.
可以和警长谈谈么
Then can we talk to the sheriff?
他今天病假
Um, he's out sick today.
好的 你看到他让他给我们电话
Well, if you see him, will you have him call us?
我们住在蓝鸟酒店
We're staying at the bluebird.
我可以拿这个么
Mind if I take this?
知道么
Know what?
你好帅
You're awesome.
谢谢
Thanks.
你也是
Um, y-you too, i guess.
是谁
Who was that?
之前的联邦探员
It, uh, those FBI guys.
他们想要什么
What did they want?
卢瑟 加兰的文件
A file, luther garland's.
警长
Sheriff?
他们知道了
They know.
他们知道你做了什么 他们是来讨债的
They know what you did, and they're gonna make you pay.
你是躲不了的
This isn't gonna work.
警徽是假的
Come on, these badges are fake.
要是我们被发现怎么办 我们要坐牢的
What if we get busted? we could go to jail.
迪恩 冷静
Dean, shh! calm down.
深呼吸
Deep breath, okay?
好点么
There. you feel better?
我们走
Just come on.
别再抓了
Don't scratch.
加兰先生
Mr. garland.
我是泰勒探员
Hi. um, i'm agent tyler.
这是佩里探员 联邦探员
This is agent perry, FBI.
我们要问你些关于你兄弟的问题
We'd like to ask you a few questions about your brother luther.
请出示你们的证件
Let me see some i.d.
当然
Certainly.
这是真的
Those are real.
当然
Obviously.
谁会假冒联邦探员
I mean, who would pretend to be an FBI agent, huh?
太傻了
That's just nutty.
你们想知道什么
What do you want to know?
呃
Uh, well…
你兄弟死于精神病
According to this, your brother luther died of physical trauma.
你不同意这个说法
You don't agree.
是的
No, i don't.
那你怎么认为
Well, then, what would you call it?
不用在意一个老人的想法
Don't matter what an old man thinks.
加兰先生
Mr. garland…
我们只想搞清你兄弟的死因
We're just trying to get the truth on your brother.
请解释一下
Please.
每个人看到卢瑟都怕
Everybody was scared of luther.
他们叫他怪胎
They called him a monster.
他太个子大了 又张的凶恶的脸
He was too big, too mean-looking.
不一样的大
Just too different.
不管他有多善良
Didn't matter he was the kindest man I ever knew.
不管他是否有没有伤害过别人
Didn't matter he'd never hurt no one.
很多人辜负过卢瑟
A lot of people failed luther.
我是其中一个
I was one of them.
我死了老婆还带着三个孩子
I was a widower with three young'uns,
所以告诉自己我无能为力
And I told myself there was nothing I could do.
加兰先生
Mr. garland, um…
你认识这女人吗
Do you recognize this woman?
杰西·奥布赖恩
It's jessie o'brien.
她丈夫弗兰克 杀了卢瑟
Her man, frank, killed luther.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
大家都知道
Everybody knows.
只是没说罢了
They just don't talk about it.
杰西是工厂里的接待员
Jessie was a receptionist at the mill.
她对卢瑟很好 所以卢瑟暗恋过她
She was always real nice to luther, and he had a crush on her.
而弗兰克对这点耿耿于怀
But frank didn't like it.
当杰西失踪时
And when jessie went missing,
弗兰克深信是卢瑟干的
Frank was sure that luther had done something to her.
结果她是自杀的 但弗兰克不知道真相
Turns out the old gal killed herself, but frank didn't know that.
卢瑟被发现时铁链正缠着他的脖子
They found luther with a chain wrapped around his neck.
他被工厂外的机器
He was dragged up and down the stretch.
拉上拉下直到他死去
Outside that plant till he was past dead.
奥布莱恩就没被逮捕吗
And o'brien was never arrested?
我向镇上的每位警官报告过
I screamed to every cop in town.
但他们不想调查弗兰克
They didn't want to look into frank.
他是社会的栋梁
He was a pillar of the community.
而我兄弟却是镇上的怪人
My brother was just the town freak.
你一定很恨弗兰克·奥布莱恩
You must have hated frank o'brien.
我恨了很久 但对于憎恨来说生命远短的多 孩子
I did for a long time, but life's too short for hate, son.
弗兰克只是一下子迷茫了
And frank wasn't thinking straight.
他老婆失踪了 他被吓坏了
His wife had vanished. he was terrified.
他只是想让卢瑟尝尝同样的耻辱 但那份恐惧
A damn shame he had to put luther through the same, but…that's fear.
连绵不绝的传播开来
It spreads and spreads.
现在我们知道这些是什么了 路疹
Now we know what these are, road rash,
我猜当卢瑟被拖曳在路上时
And I'm guessing luther swallowed some wood.
他还吞了些木屑
Chips when he was being dragged down that road.
似乎是这么回事
Makes sense.
你正慢速经历着他的死
You're experiencing his death in slow motion.
好吧 还不够慢吗
Yeah, well, not slow enough, huh?
我们去把他的骨头烧了 我就恢复健康了
Say we burn some bones and get me healthy.
迪恩 事情没这么简单
Dean, it won't be that easy.
不不不 就这么简单
No, no. it'll be that easy.
为什么没这么简单
Why wouldn't it be that easy?
卢瑟可是在马路上被拖曳的
Luther was road-hauled.
他的尸体被磨成碎块
His body was ripped to pieces.
散布在马路上的各个角落
He was probably scattered all over that road.
我们不可能找到所有残骸
There's no way we're gonna find all the remains.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
听着 我们只能从其他地方入手
Look, we'll just have to figure something else out.
你知道什么 去它妈的
You know what? screw this.
迪恩
Whoa, whoa, whoa. dean.
得了吧 我说真的 得了吧萨姆
Come on. no, i mean, come on, sam.
我们在做什么呀
What are we doing?!
我们正在猎鬼
We're hunting a ghost.
鬼 确切说到底谁在猎鬼
A ghost, exactly. who does that?
我们
Us.
我们 对啊
Us? right.
萨姆 那就是为什么我们生活一团糟
And that, sam, that is exactly why our lives suck.
我跟你说 这就是为什么我们的生活这么糟糕
得了吧 我们猎的是怪物
I mean, come on. we hunt monsters!
别这样 我们抓妖怪啊
这算什么事呀
What the hell?!
什么鬼东西
正常人看见怪物拔腿就跑
I mean, normal people, they see a monster, and they run.
我是说 正常人 看到妖怪就跑
我们咧 我们还要去找那些
But not us. No, no, no. We… we search out things.
要杀掉我们的鬼东西
that want to kill us.
要么就是要活吃了我们的
Yeah? huh? or eat us!
你知道谁才会干这事吗 神经病
You know who does that? crazy people!
我们有病
We…are insane!
你知道
You know,
我们要去吃那些恶心的东西 睡那些脏兮兮的汽车旅馆
And then there's the bad diner food and then the skeevy motel rooms.
去见那些长了些奇奇怪怪的疹子的载货车停车场女侍应
and then the truck-stop waitress with the bizarre rash.
萨姆 谁想这样过日子
I mean, who wants this life, sam?
啊 说真的
Huh? seriously?
你真的喜欢一天8个小时
Do you actually like being stuck.
和我一起关在车里
in a car with me eight hours a day,
天天如此
Every single day?
我不觉得这有什么好
I don't think so!
我开太快了
I mean, i drive too fast,
一直不断的重复听着
And I listen to the same five albums.
5张专辑还喜欢一个人独展歌喉
over and over and over again, a-and I sing along.
我很讨人厌 我自己都知道
i'm annoying.i know that.
还有你 你总是夸夸其谈
and you… you're gassy!
你吃了半个墨西哥玉米煎饼 你也中毒了
you eat half a burrito, and you get toxic!
你明白么
i mean, you know what?
你可以忘掉一切
you can forget it.
迪恩 你要去哪里
whoa, dean.where are you going?
离我远点 萨姆 好么
stay away from m sam, okay?
我已经搞定这一切了
cause I am done with it.
搞定那些魔鬼们 还有那些个地狱犬
i'm done with the monsters and… and… and the hellhounds.
幽灵疾病和操蛋的天启
and the ghost sickness and the damn apocalypse.
我功成名就了 闪人
i'm out. i'm done.quit.
我到处在找你 迪恩
i looked everywhere for you, dean.
你怎么回来的
how the hell did you get here?
用跑的
ran.
我们现在该干嘛
what do we do now?
我还有不到4小时的命了
i got less than four hours on the clock.
我要死了 萨姆
i'm gonna die, sammy.
是的
yeah, you are.
你又得回去了
you're going back.
回去
back?
底下的地狱 迪恩
downstairs, dean hell.
真是祸不单行
it's about damn time, too.
不过
truth is,
你可真是弄疼我了
you've been a real pain in my ass.
不
no!
快从我弟弟的身体里滚出来 你这狗娘养的恶魔
you get out of my brother, you evil son of a bitch!
没有谁可以附身于我 迪恩
no one's possessing me, dean.
这就是我的终极形态
this is what i'm going to become.
我就是我想要成为的模样
this is what I want to become.
你已经无能为力了
there's nothing you can do about it.
嗨嗨 迪恩
hey, hey, hey, dean.
嗨嗨嗨 迪恩
hey, dean. dean. dean.
你好 萨姆
howdy, sam.
嘿 鲍比
hey, bobby.
谢谢你那么快就赶来了
hey, thanks for coming so quick.
迪恩呢？
where's dean?
有点不舒服
home sick.
不起什么作用啊
Oh, this isn't helping.
他开始有幻觉了么
So, have his hallucinations started yet?
几小时以前开始有的
Yeah, a few hours ago.
我们还有多少时间
How we doing on time?
我们大概是周一上午8点见的验尸官
We saw the coroner about 8:00 a.m. monday morning, so, uh…
所以只有不到两个小时
Just under two hours.
你呢 有什么发现
What about you? you find anything?
这本江户时代的幽灵百科全书
This, uh, encyclopedia of spirits dates to the edo period.
你能读懂日文
You can read japanese?
看上去是 而且还会卖弄
Guess so, show-off.
不管怎么说 这本书里有我们要找的鬼魂
Anyway, this book lists a kind of ghost that could be our guy.
这种幽灵能让人得恐惧病
It, uh, infects people with fear.
名字叫 buruburu
It's called a buruburu.
书上说怎么除掉它
It say how to kill it?
和以往一样 用火烧
Same as usual, burn the remains.
很好 还有别的办法么
Wonderful. Uh…is there a plan "b"?
这毛病因恐惧而生
Well, the buruburu is born of fear.
不 应该说它就是恐惧
Hell, it is fear.
理论上讲应该能用恐惧除掉它
And the lore says we can kill it with fear.
你的意思是说我们得把它吓死
So we have to scare a ghost to death?
对
Pretty much.
那怎么可能
How the hell we gonna do that?
你在忍一会儿 好吧
So, uh, just ride out the trip, okay?
你会没事的 我们有办法了
You're… you're gonna be fine. we got a plan.
什么办法
What is it?
总之是个好办法 你等着就好了
Uh, just a good plan, all right? hang in there.
这计划可真糟
This is a terrible plan.
告诉我 糟在哪里
Yeah, tell me about it.
我知道我说过 把幽灵吓死 但这个
I know I said, "scare the ghost to death, " but this?
如果你有更好的办法 现在告诉我
You got a better idea, I'm listening.
警长
Sheriff?
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你们为什么要调查卢瑟·加兰的死因
Why are you looking into luther garland's death?
你 你病了
Hey, hey, you're… you're sick.
你病了 知道么
You're sick. you're sick, all right?
就和我一样 你得放松点儿
Just… just like me, okay? you got to relax.
弗兰克是我的老朋友
Frank o'brien was my friend.
他做错了事
So he made a mistake.
我没有抓他
So I didn't bust him.
又怎样
So what?
你们要把我也抓起来
And you're gonna bring me down over that?!
不是的
No, sir.
他们知道你做了什么
They know what you did.
离我远点
Get away from me!
- 你得冷静下来 - 别过来
- Al, you got to calm down! - Step back!
他们知道
They know…
有什么发现
Any luck?
我不知道怎么了 鲍比
I don't know what's wrong, bobby.
上次它直冲我们来的
Last time he came right at us.
现在好像
It's almost like he's, uh…
它很害怕
Like he's scared.
那怎么办
So now what?
我想我得激怒它
I guess I got to make him angry.
嘿 卢瑟
Hey, luther!
卢瑟 你小子在哪儿
Come on, luther! where the hell are you?
你在等什么
What are you waiting for?
你会回去的
You're going back.
迪恩
Hi, dean.
不 不
No. no.
没错
Yes.
就是我 莉莉丝
It's me, lilith.
我好想你啊
Oh, i missed you so much.
该回去了
It's time to go back now.
你 你不是真的
You… you are not real!
怎么了 迪恩
What's the matter, dean?
你难道不记得下面的感觉了
Don't you remember all the fun you had down there?
你肯定记得
You do remember.
在地狱里4个月就像40年一样难熬
4 months is like 40 years in hell.
度日如年 百般煎熬
Like doggy years.
每一秒你都记得
And you remember every second.
你不是真的
You are not real.
这无所谓
It doesn't matter.
你依然会死的
You're still gonna die.
依然会受到折磨
You're still gonna burn.
为什么是我
Why me?
为什么是我受到感染
Why'd I get infected?
傻瓜
Silly goose.
你知道为什么 迪恩
You know why, dean.
听听自己的心跳
Listen to your heart.
什么
What?
鲍比 快开车
Bobby, punch it!
你们开车用铁链拖死鬼魂
So you guys rode of ghosts with a chain?
刻着咒语的铁链
Iron chain etched with a spell word.
以前可真没见过
Hmm. now, that's a new one.
那是它最害怕的
It was what he was most afraid of.
其实也非常残忍
It was pretty brutal, though.
无论如何 我还活着 我们还在一起
On the upside, I'm still alive, so, uh, go, team.
是啊 你感觉怎么样
Yeah. how you feeling, by the way?
很好
Fine.
你确定 迪恩
You sure, dean?
这行可能会相当吓人
'cause this line of work can get awful scary.
我很好
I'm fine.
你们想去抓鬼么 我想去
You want to go hunting? I'll hunt.
我会杀掉任何东西
I'll kill anything.
他真可爱
Aw. he's adorable.
我该走了
I got to get out of here.
开车注意安全
You boys drive safe.
你也是 鲍比
You too, bobby.
谢谢
Hey, thanks.
那么
So, uh…
你看到什么了
So, what did you see?
我是说 最后的那会儿
Near the end, i mean.
除了一个警察打我么
Oh, besides a cop beating my ass?
认真点
Seriously.
很多烦死人的猴子
Howler monkeys.
整个屋子都是
Whole roomful of them.
- 从我身体里爬出来 - 好吧
- Those things creep the hell out of me. - Right.
其实是些很平常的东西 萨姆
No, no, just the usual stuff, sammy.
很好
all right!